_____________________

	Installation

Unpack everything to the root folder of the game, overwriting already existing GameData and Ships folders. Source folder contains the source code for the included plugins and is unnecessary for the mod to work.

Make sure you have KSP 0.22 or higher. 
Support for KSP 0.21 is discontinued, use R3.4 if a compatible version is needed. 
Support for KSP 0.20.2 is discontinued, use R3.2 if a compatible version is needed. 
Versions below 0.20.2 are incompatible completely, even with older releases.

Do not, under any circumstances, extract just GameData/B9_Aerospace/Parts folder alone, the mod won't work this way. With a proper installation, you should have multiple new folders in GameData alongside with Squad folder that was there originally. Do not try to move the part folders anywhere or sort them by category subfolders, that will break resource linking in all configs.

If you are experiencing out of memory crashes in the game with this mod, try to use low-resolution optional texture set. To install it, overwrite the GameData folder in your KSP directory with GameData from the Textures_Reduced folder.

_____________________

	About

This set of parts vastly expands a selection of parts, in particular with spaceplane components such as new engines, cockpits, wings and fuselage systems. The style was influenced by furistic concept art, modern UAV designs, some believable hard sci-fi ideas, DARPA & NASA aerospace research, and by asymmetrical shapes and faceted designs that are nowadays common everywhere from automotive industry to military aircraft. I have decided not to go overboard with realistic art style or extreme colors: my intention is to make parts which would blend seamlessly with, for example, KW Rocketry pieces. My textures are hand-painted, I’m avoiding photo-sourced areas or excessive detail like rust. Everything looks just a little bit cartoony, like a concept art, which, in my opinion, fits nicely with the general art style of KSP (most of the stock part textures were painted too). Although I’m going for higher fidelity and texture resolution, so don’t expect a 100% match – but I’m fairly satisfied with results and have already built some neat ships using them. The goal of the project is to fill every empty niche in KSP part selection and to replace every sub-par component with a new part better suited for the role.

This is the fourth milestone release of the project, now featuring 210 new parts and fully compatible with KSP 0.22. Full changelog, support and development updates can be found in the forum thread.
forum.kerbalspaceprogram.com/showthread.php/25241

_____________________

	Credits

bac9-flcl // 3D modeling, texturing 
Taverius // Configs, craft design, testing, 3D modeiing

Snjo // Firespitter.dll plugin
careo // ExsurgentEngineering.dll plugin
Kine // KineTechAnimation.dll plugin
Fel // ResGen.dll plugin

Special thanks to DYJ, C7, r4mon and Mu for their help.

_____________________


This work is shared under CC BY-NC-SA 3.0 license.